<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GoAndBe</string>
    <string name="TermsAndConditions">
    <b>TERMS AND CONDITIONS</b>\n
    Last Updated: March 8, 2026\n\n
    Welcome to GoAndBe. By creating an account, you agree to these terms.\n\n
    <b>1. ACCOUNT REGISTRATION</b>\n
    You must provide a valid email, username, and password.
    You are responsible for keeping your login credentials secure.\n\n
    <b>2. YOUR TRIPS &amp; CONTENT</b>\n
    You own the itineraries and photos you upload.
    By using the app, you grant us permission to store and display this content for your personal use. You are responsible for ensuring your content doesn\'t violate any laws.\n\n
    <b>3. DATA STORAGE</b>\n
    We aim for 100% uptime, but this app is not a permanent backup service.
    We are not liable for the loss of trip data or photos. Please keep copies of important travel documents elsewhere.\n\n
    <b>4. PROHIBITED CONDUCT</b>\n
    You may not attempt to hack the app, upload malicious code, or use the service for illegal activities.\n\n
    <b>5. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY</b>\n
    The app is provided \"as is.\" We are not responsible for travel disruptions, errors in itineraries, or data loss.\n\n
    <b>6. TERMINATION</b>\n
    We reserve the right to disable accounts that violate these terms or disrupt the service.\n\n
    <b>7. GOVERNING LAW</b>\n
    These terms are governed by the laws of Spain.
    </string>


    <string name="AboutUs">
    <b>ABOUT GOANDBE</b>\n\n
    GoAndBe was created with a simple mission: to turn your travel dreams into organized realities. We believe that the best parts of travel shouldn\'t be buried in a messy inbox or lost in a chaotic camera roll.\n\n
    <b>Our Vision</b>\n
    Whether you\'re planning a local weekend getaway or a global expedition, GoAndBe provides a dedicated space to map out your journey. By combining personal itineraries with your personal travel photos, we help you build a digital scrapbook of your adventures as they happen.\n\n
    <b>Why GoAndBe?</b>\n
    • <b>Seamless Planning:</b> Keep your dates, locations, and notes in one easy-to-access place.\n
    • <b>Visual Memories:</b> Attach photos directly to your trip timeline so you never forget a moment.\n
    • <b>Focused Experience:</b> We keep it simple—just your trips, your photos, and your next destination.\n\n
    Thank you for letting us be a part of your journey. Keep exploring!
</string>

    <string name="about_summary">GoAndBe is your ultimate travel companion, designed to help you organize itineraries and preserve memories through photos. Plan your journey, document your experiences, and revisit your adventures all in one place.</string>

    <string name="team_info"><b>Lead Developer:</b> Your Name\n<b>Design:</b> Creative Team\n<b>Support:</b> support@goandbe.com</string>

    <string name="app_version">Version 0.1.0 (Build 03.08.2026)</string>
</resources>